poemofquotes.com 2018-05-27

# Privacy Policy to PoemofQuotes.com

This policy is updated for GDPR.

This website does not collect any personal information from users, except for IP addresses and tracking cookies.  We do not collect any email addresses, names, passwords, or other information. We use tracking cookies in order to maintain session information.  IP addresses are only stored in order to defend against DoS attacks.

We have advertising and analytics partners that may track you via cookies and IP addresses.  We use Google Analytics with anonymized IP addresses, so that your individual information is not tracked.  Our advertisers may use cookies and other tracking methods. 

Need help with a poetry or literature essay? [Get a professionally written paper with citations by tomorrow for $15.](http://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=19062&brand=fiverrcpa&landingPage=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fiverr.com%2Fkirk007%2Fresearch-on-any-topic-in-english-and-literature)

Our advertisers may show a popup confirming the use of cookies when you arrive at the website. If you don't accept that, you are required to leave the site.

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at legal@westbourneinterational.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

For ads served by Google or DoubleClick Ad Exchange (which are not associated with this site), you can see additional information and manage your privacy settings here. For ads served by certain other networks, you can learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or opt-out of this type of advertising at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. If you have additional questions or comments, please contact us.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Article continues below...

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may legal@westbourneinterational.com

_Last update: Thu, 01/25/2018 - 06:09_
